VIKRY CAHYA FADHILAH, S.Kom

Jl. Pesanggrahan RT 10 / RW 05, Meruya Utara, Kembangan, Jakarta Barat Phone: +62 882-2594-8907 | Email: vikryfadhillah@gmail.com | LinkedIn: @VikryCahyaFadhillah

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced and motivated IT Support professional with 3+ years of experience providing technical assistance, cloud monitoring, and service desk leadership. Strong ability to troubleshoot network and application issues, manage service tickets, and lead support teams to meet SLAs. Known for fast learning, problem-solving, and effective communication.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Operating Systems: Windows, Linux, macOS
- Networking: Switches, Routers, Firewalls
- Remote Support: AnyDesk, TeamViewer
- Microsoft Technologies: Office 365, Windows Server
- Cloud & Virtualization: Azure VM Monitoring, AWS.
- Databases: SQL Server, PL/SQL, Toad
- Monitoring Tools: WhaTap, Elastic
- ITSM Tools: Service Desk, Ticketing Systems
- Software Deployment: ManageEngine, Antivirus Tools

SOFT SKILLS

- Team Leadership and Coordination
- Analytical Thinking & Problem Solving
- Communication and Documentation
- High Responsibility and Adaptability
- Fast Learner & Creative

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT Adira Dinamika MultiFinance, Tbk – Leader Managed Service

November 2023 – Present

- Lead service desk operations and generate monthly service reports SLA.
- Monitor Adira application performance using WhaTap and Elastic.
- Track and resolve tickets, and maintain issue knowledge base.
- Conduct SQL and PL/SQL monitoring for internal apps.

PT Indobara Borneo – System Engineer

June 2023 – July 2023

- Standardized deployment of ManageEngine and antivirus tools for 300+ users.
- Provided training and documentation for software rollout.

PT Mitra Adi Perkasa (MAP) - Helpdesk Support

February 2023 – May 2023

- Installed Office 365 and provided end-user IT support.
- Resolved service desk requests and performed troubleshooting at Head Office.

PT Mitra Integrasi Informatika – Helpdesk Support (DAAS ViSA Support TSEL) June 2022 – January 2023

- Monitor Azure virtual machines and investigate high resource usage issues.
- Troubleshoot cloud application issues remotely using AnyDesk.
- Provide technical support and assistance to users regarding ViSA TSEL apps.

PT Pactoconvex Niagatama – Video Jockey (VJ)

May 2021 - Dec 2021

Managed multimedia presentations and event looping videos during live events.

EDUCATION

Universitas Budi Luhur

Bachelor of Computer Engineering (S.Kom), 2016 – 2021

GPA: 3.27 / 4.00

SMA Daar El Qolam

2013 - 2016

CERTIFICATIONS

- Basic Computer Algorithm Competency Universitas Budi Luhur, Feb 2019
- Network and Web Security